"Only for love"
"오직 사랑을 위해서"
Part (3)
파트(3)
(The reporter has arrived for the introduction of Director Xi Sangyu )
(시상위 감독 소개를 위해 기자가 도착했습니다 .)
Isn't it one o'clock in the afternoon?
오후 1시 아닌가요?
(He arrived early, so I'll make him wait)
(그가 일찍 도착했으니 기다리게 할게요)
No need, ask him to come in
필요없어, 그 사람한테 들어오라고 해
Hello, Director Xi
안녕하세요, 시 감독님
you..
너..
My name is Xu Yuling, a reporter from Financial Introduction
저는 Financial Introduction 기자 Xu Yuling입니다.
My colleague can't come today because he has some business
내 동료는 오늘 일이 있어서 올 수 없어요
So I was transferred to do this interview
그래서 나는 이 인터뷰를 하기 위해 옮겨졌어
Thank you
감사합니다
So let's get started, director
그럼 시작하겠습니다, 감독님
Wait a minute, reporter gold
잠깐만요, 골드 기자님
Can I see your draft?
초안을 볼 수 있나요?
Got it
알았어요
(Draft interview for Xian)
(시안 인터뷰 초안)
So let's get started
그럼 시작해 볼까요
Min Yu Yun Chum is a subsidiary company of Min Yu Group
민유윤첨은 민유그룹의 자회사 입니다.
From the most influential appraisal firm in the field
해당 분야에서 가장 영향력 있는 감정평가사로부터
He is rated AA
그는 AA 등급이다
Because of his promising vision
그의 유망한 비전 때문에
It even raised the parent company's reliability standards
모회사의 신뢰성 기준까지 높였습니다.
Yun Chum's future is really promising
윤첨의 미래는 정말 유망하다
The main speaker of this interview is Min Yu Yunchum
이번 인터뷰의 메인 연사는 민유윤첨 님 입니다.
Development plan and necessary preparation for the next five years
향후 5년간의 발전 계획과 필요한 준비
including his role under the parent company
모회사에서의 그의 역할을 포함하여
Other related questions
기타 관련 질문
First I want to ask
먼저 묻고 싶습니다.
The director's point of view when he founded Min Yu Yun Chum
민유윤춤 창업 당시 감독의 시선
Subscribe to this
이것을 구독하십시오
Hello
안녕하세요
Hello, I'm a financial reporter
안녕하세요 금융 기자 입니다
Register first
먼저 등록하세요
Are all the reporters at your magazine beautiful like you?
당신 잡지의 기자들은 모두 당신처럼 아름답나요?
(Xu Yu Lin)
(서율린)
(Why is Xu Yuling's name in the guest log ?)
(게스트 로그에 왜 Xu Yuling의 이름이 있습니까?)
Thank you
감사합니다
Secretary Chan
찬 비서
About the reporter
기자 소개
Interview with director Xi scheduled for an hour today
오늘 한시간 동안 시진핑 감독 인터뷰 예정
Did it go according to plan?
계획대로 됐나요?
You have an issue, don't you?
문제가 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
Your colleague has already done the interview for you
당신의 동료가 이미 당신을 위해 인터뷰를 완료했습니다.
He came at lunchtime, which is when Director Xi is busy
시 주석이 바쁜 점심시간에 왔다.
He also said that you gave him away
그 사람도 당신이 자기를 넘겨줬다고 하더군요
Sorry , there was a disconnection in our group
죄송합니다. 그룹 연결이 끊어졌습니다.
I'm tired of coming this far
여기까지 오느라 지쳤어
I'm not tired
나는 피곤하지 않다
But..
하지만..
I have an appointment with the director Xi My Shin this afternoon
오늘 오후에 시미신 감독님과 약속이 있어요.
Director Xi has to go outside, so I will return to the reporter
시 주석이 밖에 나가야 해서 기자에게 다시 말씀드리겠습니다.
The interview is over today
오늘 면접 끝났어요
I have been waiting for this interview for a long time
나는 이 인터뷰를 오랫동안 기다렸다
I got the chance today
오늘 기회가 생겼어
Is it okay now?
이제 괜찮아요?
Director Xi has moderated the basic part of the interview
시 원장이 인터뷰의 기본 부분을 진행했다.
But five questions about Yun Chum's future
하지만 윤첨의 미래에 관한 다섯 가지 질문
You still haven't answered
아직 대답을 안 하셨어요
It will only take a little time
시간이 조금 걸릴 뿐입니다
May I
나는 할 수있다
What are those five questions?
그 다섯 가지 질문은 무엇입니까?
Question 1 : As a subsidiary company of Min Yu Group
질문 1 : 민유그룹의 자회사로서
Operated independently from the parent company
모회사로부터 독립적으로 운영됨
Do you have plans to expand into larger markets?
더 큰 시장으로 확장할 계획이 있나요?
Question 2: Regarding the cooperation between Kuen Group and Yun Chum
질문 2: Kuen Group과 Yun Chum의 협력에 관해
Besides looking to invest in more innovative areas
보다 혁신적인 분야에 투자하는 것 외에도
Any other long-term plans?
다른 장기 계획은 없나요?
Question 3 : Is it your plan to return to China for Professor Yuyo ?
질문 3: 유요교수님을 위해 중국으로 돌아가실 계획이신가요?
This is your first personal interview
첫 번째 개인 인터뷰입니다.
It is the first step towards understanding Yun Chum's exterior
윤춤의 외면을 이해하는 첫걸음이다.
So..
그래서..
i believe
나는 믿는다
The media and the public
언론과 대중
Won't you allow me to understand Yun Chum more deeply?
윤첨을 좀 더 깊이 이해할 수 있게 해주시지 않겠습니까?
followed
팔로우함
Director Xi
시 감독
Can I ask, we are going now..
물어봐도 될까요? 지금 가는데요..
(Ask my uncle to pick up the phone)
(삼촌에게 전화를 받아달라고 부탁하세요)
(Little God?)
(작은 신?)
I told him that if he doesn't listen, don't come in front of me again
안 들으면 다시는 내 앞에 오지 말라고 했어
You heard what Director Xi said
시진핑 감독이 한 말 들었지?
(Very influential)
(매우 영향력이 있음)
(If it is so influential)
(그렇게 영향력이 크다면)
(Why don't you teach yourself not to be a mistress)
( 여주인이 되지 않는 법을 스스로 가르쳐 보는 것이 어때요 ?)
Director Xi
시 감독
Driver Fan is waiting in a commercial vehicle
드라이버 팬이 상업용 차량에서 기다리고 있습니다.
Ask him to come
그에게 오라고 ​​하세요
The reporter might want to sit in this car
기자는 이 차에 앉고 싶어할 수도 있겠네요
Am I?
나는요?
They said in the car that I have to drive for two hours
차에서 2시간 운전해야 한다고 하더군요
Didn't you say you could use the time in the car earlier ?
차안에서 좀 더 일찍 시간을 보낼 수 있다고 하지 않았나요?
Of course, no problem
물론 문제없어요
(You can also say under the car)
(차 밑이라고 말할 수도 있습니다)
Director Xi
시 감독
( I don't think I should interview Shi Xian in this way )
(이런 식으로 Shi Xian을 인터뷰해서는 안 될 것 같아요)
(trust me)
(날 믿어)
(Xiang is a man too)
(샹 도 남자예요)
(A man cannot refuse such an approach )
(남자는 그런 접근을 거부할 수 없다)
(Isn't the Shanshan method useless?)
(샨샨 방식은 쓸모없는거 아닌가요?)
Is it cold?
그것은 차갑습니까?
It's not cold
춥지 않아요
Put down the torch
횃불을 내려놔
Well done, Director Xi
수고하셨어요 시 감독님
(Just saying I'm not cold doesn't mean I'm hot)
(춥지 않다고 해서 덥다는 뜻은 아니다)
My time is limited
내 시간은 제한되어 있습니다.
Director Xi Before we officially start
시 감독 본격적으로 시작하기 전에
Let's talk about the other first , so it's easy
다른 얘기부터 먼저 해보죠 , 그러니까 쉽죠
What do you want to say?
말하고 싶은게 뭡니까?
Director Xi will certainly rarely accept an interview
시 주석은 확실히 인터뷰를 거의 받아들이지 않을 것이다
Usually, before we start the interview, we get to know the interviewee a little bit
보통 인터뷰를 시작하기 전, 인터뷰 대상자에 대해 조금씩 알아가게 됩니다.
So let's introduce ourselves
그럼 자기소개를 해보자
We should get to know each other a little
우리는 서로를 조금 알아가야 해요
I am a reporter from Keng Shuyi's financial introduction
저는 Keng Shuyi의 금융 소개 기자입니다
I am really honored to interview Director Xi today
오늘 시 주석과 인터뷰하게 되어 정말 영광입니다
Shi Xiang, 27, is the CEO of Min Yu Yun Chum
Shi Xiang(27세)은 Min Yu Yun Chum의 CEO입니다.
(Why do I think of such a bad method ?)
(나는 왜 이런 나쁜 방법을 생각하는 걸까?)
Director Xi is really young and promising
시진핑 감독은 정말 젊고 유망 하다.
(I just said this)
(방금 이렇게 말했어요)
In fact, I was waiting for you at Wanara Farm the first time
사실 처음에 와나라팜에서 기다리고 있었어요
I was really lucky
정말 운이 좋았어
I heard that director Shao Kuon of the Kuon group will also be there
쿠온그룹 샤오쿠온 감독도 참석한다고 들었는데
Because you and he are close
너와 그 사람은 가깝기 때문에
Enough to encourage
격려해주기엔 충분해요
Although he said that he rarely attends such events
그는 그런 행사에 거의 참석하지 않는다고 말했지만
I can't tell if fate favors me
운명이 나에게 유리한지 알 수 없다
Anyway, for our journalists, publication day is a holiday
아무튼 우리 기자들에겐 출판일이 휴일이다
Unfortunately, I was really lucky
안타깝게도 정말 운이 좋았습니다
I didn't get the chance to interview you, but I got the chance to meet you
인터뷰할 기회는 없었지만 만날 기회가 생겼어요
So, the cooperation between Shin and the Ku group
그래서 신씨와 구그룹의 협력은
Will it be officially announced soon?
곧 공식적으로 발표되겠죠?
Are you going to expand into areas of mutual interest ?
상호 관심 분야로 확장할 예정입니까?
Director Xi, what did I say wrong?
시 감독님, 제가 뭘 잘못 말했나요?
Why do you think Kum Group wants to join Yun Chum?
금그룹이 왜 윤첨에 합류하고 싶어 한다고 생각하시나요 ?
What do you think Yun Chum and Kum Group will do?
윤첨과 금그룹은 어떻게 할 것이라고 생각하시나요?
Have you finished asking?
질문은 끝났나요?
Director Xi, I have one more question
시 위원장님 질문이 하나 더 있습니다
Why didn't you stay at Min Yu Group at that time?
당시 왜 민유그룹에 머물지 않았나요 ?
Did you choose to start your own business?
자신의 사업을 시작하기로 결정하셨나요?
Did your father support your decision?
아버지는 당신의 결정을 지지하셨나요?
I am getting old
나는 늙어 가고있다
I can't handle many things anymore
더 이상 많은 일을 처리할 수 없어요
This time, Min Yu was able to survive thanks to some old friends
이번에 민유는 오랜 친구들 덕분에 살아남을 수 있었다
Min Yu's future
민유의 미래
It depends on you
그것은 당신 한테 달려 있어요
In fact, my husband is more suitable than me
사실 나보다 남편이 더 잘 어울리는데
But your lineage is Xi
하지만 당신의 혈통은 Xi입니다
Yu Yu needs you
유유는 당신이 필요합니다
Her husband is a member of the Xi family
남편은 시진핑 가문 출신
I still want to do something meaningful and happy for myself
그래도 나 자신을 위해 의미 있고 행복한 일을 하고 싶다.
How do you..
어떻게..
Have you thought it through?
생각해 보셨나요?
I have thought it through
나는 그것을 깊이 생각했다
This road..
이 길..
It will be very difficult
매우 어려울 것입니다
I know
알아요
But someone has to step up
하지만 누군가는 나서야 해
You..
너..
I will be retiring soon
나는 곧 은퇴할 것이다
The house is the car
집이 차다
You will not need to use the latter
후자를 사용할 필요는 없습니다
You take it
당신은 그것을 받아
Thank you, father
고마워요, 아버지
Two hours have passed
두 시간이 지났어요
You can return now
지금 돌아가셔도 됩니다
( How do you get back from such a remote place ?)
(이렇게 먼 곳에서는 어떻게 돌아오나요?)
(Do you have to ride a horse?)
(말을 타야 하나요?)
(Shi Xian is very angry)
(시시안은 매우 화가 났습니다)
( I want you to give up in this remote place )
(이 먼 곳에서는 포기해줬으면 좋겠어)
(absolutely impossible)
(절대 불가능)
(I came by this car and must return with this car)
(나는 이 차로 왔고 이 차로 돌아와야 한다)
Director Xi Sing's voice is very good to listen to
시싱감독님 목소리가 너무 듣기 좋네요
Through some of your answers
귀하의 답변 중 일부를 통해
Can we use it as an audio file in our digital magazine ?
디지털 매거진의 오디오 파일로 사용할 수 있나요?
I want to have my full view
내 전체 모습을 보고 싶어
So it means that I got it
그러니까 내가 받았다는 뜻이야
Wait a minute, Director Xi
잠깐만 시진핑 감독
I have one last question
마지막 질문이 있어요
say
말하다
Do you have a girlfriend?
여자친구가 있나요?
This question is to satisfy the curiosity of our readers
이 질문은 독자들의 호기심을 충족시키기 위한 것 입니다.
It doesn't matter if Director Xi doesn't want to answer
시 주석이 대답을 원하지 않아도 상관없다.
Actually, my last question
사실 마지막 질문이에요
A young investment company like Min Yu Yun Chum
민유윤첨 같은 젊은 투자회사
Why did you decide to invest in Le Ann technology ?
왜 Le Ann 기술에 투자하기로 결정하셨나요?
Because the long-term research and development chain will not be immediately profitable
장기적인 연구 개발 체인은 즉시 수익성이 높지 않기 때문에
Aren't you worried?
걱정되지 않나요?
Is this question just to satisfy readers' curiosity?
이 질문은 단지 독자의 호기심을 충족시키기 위한 것입니까?
As a financial reporter
재무 기자로서
After researching various sources of information
다양한 정보 출처를 조사한 후
A scholarly review
학술적 검토
Xian
시안
This is it
이거 야
Teacher Kun
쿤 선생님
Hello, I'm Kung Shuyi, a reporter from Financial Introduction
안녕하세요 금융소개 기자 쿵슈이 입니다
Do you know me?
저를 아시나요?
In university, I majored in journalism but minored in finance
대학에서는 저널리즘을 전공했지만 금융을 부전공했습니다.
During the first class of the finance lesson, the teacher talked about my uncle
금융수업 첫 수업시간에 선생님께서 삼촌에 대해 말씀하셨어요.
And I work with my uncle every day
그리고 난 매일 삼촌이랑 일해
On the walls of our office
우리 사무실 벽에는
There is a magazine cover picture of uncle and teacher Shi Wan Kuon
삼촌이자 선생님인 시완쿠온(Shi Wan Kuon)의 잡지 표지 사진이 있습니다
So, my uncle's name has been with me throughout my university life
그래서 삼촌의 이름은 대학 생활 내내 나와 함께했습니다.
My uncle's existence is a companion in my daily work life
삼촌의 존재는 나의 일상생활의 동반자 이다
Even though he doesn't appear in public much now, everyone knows him
지금은 대중 앞에 많이 모습을 드러내지 않지만 모두가 그를 알고 있다 .
Uncle's reputation is unshakable like Titaung
삼촌의 평판은 Titaung처럼 흔들리지 않습니다.
I just said, what is your name?
방금 말했잖아요, 이름이 뭐예요?
Keng Shuyi, right?
켕슈이 맞죠?
Yes
예
Keng Shuyi
켕슈이
I remember you
나는 당신을 기억합니다
I have read three or four of your articles
나는 당신의 기사를 서너 개 읽었습니다.
Not bad writing
나쁘지 않은 글이네요
It is serious and has a position
심각하고 입장이 있다
Unexpectedly, when I met her in person, she was a little girl
의외로 그녀를 직접 만났을 때 그녀는 어린 소녀였습니다.
Too much praise
칭찬이 너무 많아
I think I came to you alone again
또 혼자 너한테 온 것 같아
I didn't prepare anything
아무것도 준비하지 않았어요
Girl, don't blame me for that
자기야, 그걸로 나를 비난하지 마세요
This guy has never brought any girl here
이 남자는 여기 여자를 데려온 적이 없어
- Uncle Le Ku, in fact, he is.. - My God..
- 르쿠 삼촌은 사실.. - 맙소사..
This place is very beautiful
이곳은 매우 아름답습니다
These horses are also very beautiful
이 말들도 ​​정말 아름다워요
I heard that my uncle's greatest hobby is horse riding
삼촌의 가장 큰 취미는 승마라고 들었는데
There will be quite a few horses
말이 꽤 많을 것이다
This is not my best horse yet
이것은 아직 내 최고의 말이 아니다
The best horses are inside
최고의 말은 내부에 있습니다
Is it still there?
아직도 거기 있나요?
Do you want to see?
당신이보고 싶어?
Followed the Shiyan girl
Shiyan 소녀를 따라갔습니다.
come with me
날 따라와
Why?
왜?
Is there a problem with Director Xi?
시진핑 감독에게 문제가 있는 걸까?
Teacher Kuon invited me
쿠온 선생님께서 저를 초대해 주셨어요.
What is there to fear?
두려워할 것이 무엇입니까?
Mixing me with horse feed is not enough to feed the horses
나에게 말 사료를 섞어 주는 것만으로는 말들에게 먹이를 주기에 부족하다
I'll go in and change my shirt
나 들어가서 셔츠 갈아입을게
I will wait
나는 기다릴 것이다
Has Shi Xiang entered?
시샹이 들어갔나요?
How long have you known Xian?
시안을 알고 지낸 지 얼마나 됐어요?
Not too long ago
얼마 지나지 않아
It seems so
그런 것 같아요
Can you ride a horse?
너 말 탈 수 있니?
I don't know how to ride
타는 방법을 모르겠어요
Inside were some old riding clothes that my wife wore
그 안에는 아내가 입었던 낡은 승마복이 들어 있었습니다.
If you don't mind, you can wear it
상관없으면 입어도 돼
You should try it when it arrives
도착하면 꼭 드셔보세요
you do not say
당신은 말하지 않는다
This side
이 쪽
My wife's physique is not that different from yours
내 아내의 체격은 당신과 크게 다르지 않습니다
Enough with this
이걸로 충분해
Thank you, Mr. Kun
고마워요, 쿤 씨
I will wait for you outside
밖에서 기다릴게요
I can't hear a sound
소리가 들리지 않아요
It's enough to leave
떠나는 것만으로도 충분해
Director Xi
시 감독
I don't wear this belt
나는 이 벨트를 착용하지 않습니다
Can you teach me?
가르쳐 주실 수 있나요?
(You still want to fool me)
(당신은 여전히 ​​나를 속이고 싶어합니다)
If you can't wear it, don't ride it
입을 수 없다면 타지 마세요
Mark said once
마크가 한 번 말했지
If a woman wants to pursue a man
여자가 남자를 쫓고 싶다면
There is no wall that she cannot overcome
그녀가 넘지 못할 벽은 없다
There is no fortress she can break down
그녀가 무너뜨릴 수 있는 요새는 없어요
There is no worry he can't shake off
그 사람이 떨쳐버릴 수 없는 걱정은 없어
Even a god cannot control him
신조차도 그를 통제할 수는 없다
So what am I now facing an impenetrable fortress?
그렇다면 나는 지금 뚫을 수 없는 요새에 직면해 있는 걸까요?
Dangerous trip?
위험한 여행?
Wrath of God?
하나님의 진노?
Not one
하나도 아니야
A small rejection
작은 거절
You can cross over
건너가시면 됩니다
come come
어떻게
This horse is the most delicate
이 말이 가장 섬세해요
After that, ask Shi Xian to teach you
그 후 Shi Xian에게 가르쳐달라고 부탁하세요
come come
어떻게
Be careful
조심하세요
A really handsome prince
정말 잘생긴 왕자님
So the horse
그래서 말
Or a princess?
아니면 공주?
Really clever
정말 영리해요
It looks so delicate to me..
제가 보기엔 너무 섬세해 보이네요..
We..
우리..
So, Director Xi, please teach me how to ride a horse
그러니까 시 감독님, 저에게 말 타는 법을 가르쳐 주세요.
Go up
위로 가다
Lead the director
감독을 이끌어라
In this way, you will be able to teach horse riding
이렇게 하면 승마를 배울 수 있습니다.
Relax and learn
긴장을 풀고 배우세요
Well done
잘하셨어요
I 'm a little nervous because it's my first time riding a horse
처음 타는 말이라 좀 긴장되요
Be sure to sit down
꼭 앉아보세요
What
무엇
Slowly slowly
천천히 천천히
Slowly
느리게
Why don't you?
왜 안 그래?
No, I..
아니, 난..
Just get the experience
경험을 쌓으시면 됩니다
It is the most delicate horse in the whole horse race
경마 전체에서 가장 섬세한 말입니다.
I am also very close to you
나는 또한 당신과 매우 가깝습니다.
Asking you to teach a girl to ride a horse
소녀에게 말 타는 법을 가르쳐 달라고 부탁함
Why scare him?
왜 겁을 주나요?
He is brave and doesn't get scared easily
그는 용감하고 쉽게 겁을 내지 않는다
Before, I asked you to rest on the horse slope
예전에 말 경사면에서 쉬어달라고 했더니
I don't come because I have too much work
일이 너무 많아서 안 오는데
Why did you suddenly have time today and bring the girl?
오늘 갑자기 시간이 나서 그 여자를 데려온 이유는 무엇입니까?
Suddenly wanted to come
갑자기 오고 싶었는데
This girl is quite interesting
이 여자 꽤 흥미롭다
It's definitely the way you like it
확실히 당신이 좋아하는 방식이군요
is that so
그렇습니까?
It's not about anything now
지금은 아무것도 아닌데
Not now, but if it continues, something will happen
지금은 아니지만 계속된다면 무슨 일이 일어날 것입니다.
Did you do such a rough road on purpose?
일부러 이렇게 험난한 길을 가신 건가요?
He even mocked me in front of Mr. Ku
심지어 구씨 앞에서 나를 조롱하기도 했다.
Is it even human?
심지어 인간인가요?
Mark can't always be right
마크가 항상 옳을 수는 없어
At least I couldn't even pass the saddle of the horse in front of me
적어도 내 앞에 있는 말 안장조차 지나칠 수 없었지
gone
다 쓴
Yes
예
A lot of things may be nothing at first
많은 것들이 처음에는 아무것도 아닐 수도 있다
But as it goes on, there are many possibilities
하지만 진행하다 보면 가능성은 많아진다
You're talking
당신이 말하는거야
Le Ann technology?
르앤 기술?
In all cases
모든 경우에
Yun Chum is the same
윤찬도 마찬가지야
I have heard from Kukyi
쿠키한테 들었어
I was a little worried about you at first
처음엔 네가 좀 걱정됐어
But now it looks like I'm too nervous
그런데 지금은 너무 긴장한 것 같아
Xian
시안
The path you want to take
당신이 가고 싶은 길
It's long and not easy
길고 쉽지 않네요
Min Yu has just passed a mountain and decided to establish Yun Chum
민유는 산을 넘고 윤춤을 창업하기로 결심했습니다.
Longtian and others helped Min Yu survive
Longtian과 다른 사람들은 Min Yu의 생존을 도왔습니다.
Now help you too
이제 당신도 도와주세요
You must remember this grace
이 은혜를 기억해야 합니다
Yun Chum wants stability more than anything else at this stage
윤춤은 현 단계에서 무엇보다 안정을 원한다.
You don't need to make Luang Thanh and other people angry
Luang Thanh과 다른 사람들 을 화나게 할 필요는 없습니다.
If they're not happy, you're going to have a hard time
그 사람들이 행복하지 않으면 당신도 힘들어질 거예요
I remember
기억해
So I have to do better
그러니 더 잘해야 해
As long as the decisions are right, all dissatisfaction will be temporary
결정이 올바른 한 모든 불만은 일시적입니다.
I also heard about Leyin's case
레이인 사건도 들었는데
It's a good choice to invest in them to some extent
어느 정도 투자하는 것이 좋은 선택입니다
As soon as the funds came from Kuon Group
쿠온그룹에서 자금이 들어오자마자
Yun Chum can invest in both companies
윤첨은 두 회사 모두에 투자할 수 있다
No need to create unnecessary tension
불필요한 긴장감을 조성할 필요는 없습니다
They are all your father's old friends
그 사람들은 모두 네 아버지의 오랜 친구들이야
No need to embarrass them
그들을 당황하게 할 필요는 없어
Uncle, I understand what Uncle wants to say
삼촌, 삼촌이 하고 싶은 말은 이해해요
But Yun Chum is still very young
하지만 윤첨은 아직 너무 어리다.
I want him to be pure and good at one thing
나는 그 사람이 순수하고 한 가지를 잘 했으면 좋겠다.
We don't want to change our philosophy and purpose to please others
우리는 다른 사람을 기쁘게 하기 위해 우리의 철학과 목적을 바꾸고 싶지 않습니다.
Because of Min Yu's crisis
민유의 위기 때문에
I understood
나는 이해했다
A modern company needs more professional and refined management
현대 기업에는 보다 전문적이고 세련된 경영이 필요합니다
Have you come back to avoid it?
그것을 피해 돌아왔나요?
What are you doing now?
뭐하세요?
It has been three or four days since I returned
돌아온지 3~4일 됐는데
I'm wasting my life doing nothing
나는 아무것도 하지 않고 내 인생을 낭비하고 있다
I plan to get him a job to gain experience
나는 그에게 직업을 주어 경험을 쌓을 계획이다
You just said it yourself
방금 직접 말했잖아
Sometimes some people may be nothing at first, right?
때로는 어떤 사람들은 처음에는 아무것도 아닐 수도 있습니다. 그렇죠?
But as it goes on, there are many possibilities
하지만 진행하다 보면 가능성은 많아진다
Xiao Yue is a smart child
Xiao Yue는 똑똑한 아이입니다
If you train well, you can become very good
훈련을 잘 하면 아주 훌륭해질 수 있다
It is possible
것이 가능하다
I just don't know how to trigger those possibilities
나는 그런 가능성을 어떻게 촉발시키는지 모르겠어요
Or ask him to join a group of dicks
아니면 그에게 거시기 그룹에 가입하라고 요청하세요
To force him to work at the barn?
헛간에서 일하도록 강요하려고요?
So I don't know who should work for whom
그래서 누가 누구를 위해 일해야 할지 모르겠어요
Uncle didn't know that Ku Kyi always wanted him
삼촌은 Ku Kyi가 항상 그를 원했다는 것을 몰랐습니다.
That's right
좋아요
If you really want to train him
정말로 그를 훈련시키고 싶다면
He has to go to a completely unfamiliar environment
그는 전혀 낯선 환경으로 가야만 한다
This poor boy can neither study nor play sports
이 불쌍한 소년은 공부도 할 수 없고 운동 도 할 수 없습니다
What company would want him?
어떤 회사가 그를 원할까요?
Did Ekanta hire him as a bribe?
Ekanta가 그를 뇌물로 고용했습니까?
Don't tell the child that
아이에게 그런 말을 하지 마세요
Xiao Yue is smart, happy, and emotionally mature
Xiao Yue는 똑똑하고 행복하며 감정적으로 성숙합니다.
I like to talk to people
나는 사람들과 이야기하는 것을 좋아한다
Ask him to be a reporter
그에게 기자가 되어달라고 부탁해
Did he study journalism abroad?
그는 해외에서 저널리즘을 공부했나요?
Major and work bite
전공과 업무
Reporter
보고자
A man like him?
그 사람 같은 사람?
So what kind of person do you think a journalist should be?
그렇다면 기자는 어떤 사람이 되어야 한다고 생각하시나요?
Xin can win the best actor Oscar in China
Xin은 중국 최고의 배우 오스카상을 수상할 수 있습니다
This is the form
이것은 형태입니다
It was as if he had just done such an act
방금 그런 행동을 한 것 같았어요
I think I might have to give it a try
한번 시도해 봐야 할 것 같아요
I had to try it
나는 그것을 시도해야했다
I have a journalist friend who can help
도움을 줄 수 있는 기자 친구가 있어요
Do you also know the reporters of U Le Koon ?
유르쿤 기자도 아시나요?
The reporters know me
기자들이 나를 알아요
Still watching
아직 시청 중
You want to see my shame
나의 부끄러움을 보고 싶나요?
Let's see
보자
You don't have much chance anymore
더 이상 기회가 많지 않아요
Don't think about seeing me again
다시 만날 생각은 하지 마
Chan Shanro
찬 샨로
Director Xi
시 감독
Secretary Chan said there was an important matter at the company
찬 비서가 회사에서 중요한 일이 있다고 하더군요
Send the reporter back first
기자를 먼저 돌려보내라
all right
괜찮은
(Isn't this man hungry?)
(이 사람 배고프지 않나요?)
(Interviewing for two hours , riding a horse for an entire evening)
(2시간 동안 인터뷰 , 저녁 내내 말 타기)
(If you forget to eat it on its own, keep it)
(그 자체로 먹는 것을 잊었다면 보관하십시오)
(How do you not know a little about society?)
(어떻게 사회에 대해 조금도 모르시나요?)
(He doesn't want to throw me a meal, so I'll buy it for him.)
(그 사람이 나한테 밥을 주고 싶어하지 않아서 내가 사줄게.)
(but the way he works)
(하지만 그가 일하는 방식은)
(quite attractive)
(꽤 매력적)
I'm sorry, Director Shiro
미안해요, 시로 감독님
I have to go because there is a matter with Director Xi
시진핑 감독님과 일이 있어서 가야 해요
Long Phang, I will go first
롱팡아 내가 먼저 갈게
You send him home
당신은 그 사람을 집으로 보내요
When he wakes up, see what else he needs
그가 깨어나면 그에게 필요한 것이 무엇인지 살펴보세요
Send it home
집으로 보내세요
Well done, Director Xi
수고하셨어요 시 감독님
I don't need it anymore, thanks
더 이상 필요하지 않습니다. 감사합니다.
(What a strange friendship)
(정말 이상한 우정이다)
(When I think about it, I don't get impatient)
(생각해보면 조급해지지 않아요)
(He gave me a car and ran away. How big is that?)
(그는 나에게 차를 주고 도망갔다. 얼마나 큰가?)
How did you fall asleep in the interviewer's car?
면접관 차에서 어떻게 잠들었나요?
The interviewer is Shi Xian
면접관은 Shi Xian입니다.
It never happened before
이전에는 그런 일이 없었어요
Very unprofessional
매우 비전문적
I fell asleep so soundly
너무 푹 잠들었어요
I don't know if I have done something shameful yet
내가 아직 부끄러운 짓을 했는지는 모르겠지만
On the threshold
문턱에서
The earring is only 25 yuan per side
귀걸이는 한 면당 25위안입니다.
Leave it as a gift for teaching me
가르쳐준 선물로 남겨주세요
Director Xi
시 감독
Thank you very much for coming to see me this time
이번에 저를 보러 와주셔서 정말 감사드립니다
sit down
앉아
But
하지만
Some things I really can't control
내가 정말로 통제할 수 없는 몇 가지 것들
Anyway, I'm not the only one
어쨌든 나만 그런 게 아니잖아
I can't just think about my dreams
내 꿈만 생각할 수는 없어
I understand
이해합니다
Yun Chum can give you what Lei Ying can give you
레이잉이 당신에게 줄 수 있는 것을 윤첨도 당신에게 줄 수 있습니다
You should also understand
너도 이해해야지
Yun Chum only because of his sincerity towards Le Ann
윤첨은 단지 르앤을 향한 진심 때문이다.
Le Yin offered Le An a fifty million purchase price
Le Yin은 Le An에게 5천만 달러의 구매 가격을 제시했습니다.
I understand, but
이해합니다만
Fifty million is quite attractive to Le Ann at the moment
현재 Le Ann에게는 5천만 달러 가 상당히 매력적입니다.
Director Chen, you also know that Leying still needs investment from us
첸 이사님, Leying이 아직 우리의 투자가 필요하다는 걸 아시죠?
Not to mention they don't have enough funds for this purchase
말할 것도 없이 이 구매에 필요한 자금이 충분하지 않습니다.
If you look at the long term
장기적으로 보면
Your team should not be at the helm of a combined company at this stage
이 단계에서는 귀하의 팀이 합병된 회사의 책임자가 되어서는 안 됩니다.
Yun Chum wants to establish China Chip with Le An
윤첨, 레안과 함께 차이나 칩 설립 원해
So what is the best fit for Le Ann at this stage?
그렇다면 이 단계에서 Le Ann에게 가장 적합한 것은 무엇입니까?
Certainly financial support is not for sale
물론 재정적 지원은 판매용이 아닙니다.
Director Xi, you know our value
시 감독님, 우리의 가치를 아시나요?
But we have been discussing with Yun Chum for some time now
그런데 우리는 윤첨씨와 한동안 논의를 해왔습니다.
There was no progress in our cooperation
우리의 협력에는 아무런 진전이 없었습니다
Now our team is in urgent need of funding for the breakthrough
이제 우리 팀은 획기적인 발전을 위한 자금이 시급히 필요합니다.
My team has no answer
우리팀은 답이 없네
Give me some time and I will quickly work out the details of the collaboration
시간을 좀 주시면 협업 세부사항을 신속하게 처리하겠습니다.
Solve these problems together
이러한 문제를 함께 해결해 보세요.
(The legs are already black from the horse's saddle )
(말 안장으로 인해 다리는 이미 검게 변했습니다.)
( I'm tired to death because of an article)
( 기사 때문에 피곤해 죽겠다)
(it's really not easy)
(정말 쉽지 않네요)
(When I go, I will have a massage)
(내가 가면 마사지를 받을 것이다)
(I'm not going to finish the article)
(글을 끝내지 않겠습니다)
Not a bad article, I'm tired
나쁜 기사는 아니고 피곤해요
I'm not tired, it's very good to write
피곤하지도 않고 쓰기 너무 좋아요
Why is there more to say?
할 말이 더 많은 이유는 무엇입니까?
Sister, I have a few ideas
언니, 나한테 몇 가지 생각이 있어요
In this interview, Xian shared many innovative views
이번 인터뷰에서 Xian은 많은 혁신적인 견해를 공유했습니다.
It will appeal to most young readers
대부분의 젊은 독자들에게 어필할 것입니다.
But he is always secretive, so many people want to know about him
하지만 그는 항상 비밀스러운 사람이어서 많은 사람들이 그에 대해 알고 싶어합니다.
So, I want to add the audio file of Shi Xian to the digital magazine
그래서 디지털 매거진에 Shi Xian의 오디오 파일을 추가하고 싶습니다.
Shuyi's idea is good
슈이님 아이디어 좋네요
But upgrading a digital magazine is not an easy task
하지만 디지털 매거진을 업그레이드하는 것은 쉬운 일이 아닙니다.
It needs a lot of manpower and money
인력과 자금이 많이 필요하다.
Who will release the audio file you just mentioned ?
방금 언급한 오디오 파일은 누가 공개합니까?
I understand, sister
이해해요 언니
So we have to catch up with the reading habits of our readers
그래서 우리는 독자들의 독서 습관을 따라잡아야 합니다.
You should take the lead
당신이 주도해야합니다
That will increase sales and upgrade the magazine
그러면 판매량이 늘어나고 잡지도 업그레이드 됩니다.
Once the magazine has been upgraded and given a more diverse presentation style
매거진이 업그레이드되어 더욱 다양한 프레젠테이션 스타일이 제공되면
It can improve the reading experience of readers
독자의 독서 경험을 향상시킬 수 있습니다
Can give an effective response
효과적인 대응을 할 수 있다
That's why they want to pay for our content
그것이 바로 그들이 우리 콘텐츠에 대한 비용을 지불하려는 이유입니다.
Once we get the funding , we can upgrade and redesign the magazine
자금을 확보하면 잡지를 업그레이드하고 다시 디자인할 수 있습니다.
To produce the audio file
오디오 파일을 제작하려면
I learned the basics online
온라인으로 기초를 배웠어요
I can do it now
이제 할 수 있어요
You are really persistent
당신은 정말 끈기 있는 사람이에요
I will speak to the editor-in-chief first
편집장한테 먼저 얘기 좀 할게
I will try to help you do this one
나는 당신이 이 일을 할 수 있도록 도와주려고 노력할 것입니다
Thank you sister
고마워 누이